site2sms.org 2014-04-30

# Privacy Policy Site2SMS - India's Largest Messaging Service

Privacy Policy

if you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at support@site2sms.com 

At www.site2sms.com, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by www.site2sms.com and how it is used. 

Log Files   
Like many other Web sites, www.site2sms.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable. 

Cookies and Web Beacons   
www.site2sms.com does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser. 

DoubleClick DART Cookie   
Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on www.site2sms.com.   
Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to www.site2sms.com and other sites on the Internet.   
Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL - http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html 

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include Google Adsense   
These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on www.site2sms.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.  
www.site2sms.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers. 

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. www.site2sms.com's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.   
If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites.   
Lohchab Network and its subsidiaries (www.Site2Sms.com) takes your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy.You are advised to please read the Privacy Policy carefully. By accessing the services provided by Site2Sms.com you agree to the collection and use of your data by Site2Sms in the manner provided in this Privacy Policy.   
If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should contact Site2Sms Customer Support Desk at support@site2sms.com 

What this Privacy Policy Covers   
This Privacy Policy covers Site2SMS.com treatment of personally identifiable information that Site2SMS collects when you are on the site, and when you use Site2SMS services. This policy also covers Site2SMS's treatment of any personally identifiable information that Site2SMS's business partners share with Site2Sms.   
This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that Lohchab Network or Site2Sms does not own or control, or to people that Site2Sms does not employ or manage.  
What information is or may be collected from you   
We will automatically receive and collect certain anonymous information in standard usage logs through our Web server, including computer-identification information obtained from "cookies," sent to your browser from:   
an IP address, assigned to the computer which you use the domain server through which you access our service the type of computer you're using the type of web browser you're using We may collect the following personally identifiable information about you: name including first and last name alternate email address mobile phone number and contact details ZIP/Postal code demographic profile (like your age, gender, occupation, education, address and durables owned); preferences and interests (such as news, sports, travel and so on); financial information (like account or credit card numbers); and opinions of features on our websites.   
How is this information used   
We use your email address to send you:   
Password reminder and registration confirmation   
Special offers   
News letters   
Changes in the service's policy or terms of use   
Event based communications such as order information, renewal notices, invites, reminders etc.   
Note: We send users newsletters and updates upon registration. We send newsletters and/or promotional emails on behalf of our alliance partners.   
We use your Mobile number to send you:   
Password reminder and Registration confirmation   
Special feature updates   
Event based services such as renewal notices, invites, email alerts , reminders etc.,   
Promotional SMSes on behalf of our alliance partners 

We use your personal information to:   
help us provide personalized features tailor our sites to your interest to get in touch with you in the case of password retrieval and policy changes to provide the services requested by you to preserve social history as governed by existing law or policy   
We use contact information internally to:   
direct our efforts for product improvement contact you as a survey respondent notify you if you win any contest; and send you promotional materials from our contest sponsors or advertisers 

Information Sharing And disclosure   
We do not share or rent your email addresses or Mobile number with third parties except our advertisers / partners.   
Site2Sms will send personally identifiable information about you to other companies or people when:   
We need to share the information with certain service partners in order to respond to your comments or to resolve service issues.   
We respond to requests from any Indian or foreign government, security, defence, revenue, regulatory or other authority, agency or officer;   
We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable and email address information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Web site.   
We share your information with advertisers on an aggregate basis only.   
Security   
We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information and email address, Mobile Number submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. Youe Site2Sms Account is password protected.No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information and email address and Mobile Number, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. 

If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can send email us at support@Site2Sms.com   
Your Preferences to Edit and Delete Your Account Information   
Site2Sms gives you the ability to edit your Site2Sms account information and preferences at any time, including whether you want Site2Sms to contact you about specials and new products. Site2Sms is not responsible and will not be liable for the accuracy, completeness, veracity and reliability of any information including any customized information which may be accessed by or provided to you, which could vary depending on your Site2Sms Account Information and preferences including your browser preferences. Also, you can always opt out from receiving emails by choosing unsubscribe link from email you received. We generally, remove your mail id from our mailing list in 5-6 business days.   
You may request us to delete your account by emailing to support@Site2Sms.com. We send you a 4 digit unique number to your Mobile number, using this you can unsubscribe/delete your account. 

Policy Updates   
We reserve the right to change or update this policy at any time by placing a prominent notice on our site. Such changes shall be effective immediately upon posting to this site.   
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, or by means of a notice on our homepage. 

If you have questions or suggestions contact us.   
Contact Information   
You can contact us at:   
Lohchab Network   
2008, Railway Road   
Narela Delhi - 110040 (India)   
Tel: +911130130202   
Email: info@site2sms.com
